

T'Keyah Marshall

UX Designer

Snapshot

I am a visual-centered retail professional of 10+ years with a broad digital background. My interest in creative software and media has inspired me to pivot into the design space. I am seeking a UX Design role to collaborate creatively and utilize Social Media and Marketing training to create an impactful user experience.

Skillset

HTML • CSS • JS • UX/UI •

Github • Adobe Suite •

Wordpress • Figma • Procreate •

Editing • Responsive Design •

Sketch • Visual Merchandising •

Product Knowledge • Onboarding

Contact

portfolio tkeyahnyree.github.io email tknyma@gmail.com



Experience

Google UX Design Professional Program Fall 2021 | Coursera

I have completed multiple design projects and studied the essential roles involved in the UX process.

- -Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design
- -UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate
- -Conduct UX Research and Test Early Concepts
- -Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes
- -Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma
- -Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD
- -Design a User Experience for Social Good

Footwear Buyer

2017 - present | SnipesUSA

I create digital training materials for Aptos and RMS merchandising and inventory reporting applications. Purchasing allows me to research consumer trends and spending habits to assemble trend boards and curate accurate product assortment. In preceding roles, I have produced last minute store communication graphics in response to delayed product releases.

Visual Merchandise Manager 2016 - 2017 | L'Oreal #MAKEUP

I designed marketing materials for social media, email advertising and floorset visuals for concept store #MAKEUP. Operational contribution included digital creation of KPI tools such as daily sales planner and conversion tracker. Effectively planned and executed visual directives.

Assistant Store Manager

2012 - 2015 | ICING by Claire's

I rendered location-based promotional flyer mockups for partnered and seasonal marketing events. Developed digital lookbooks for consumer personas.

Education

B.A. Liberal Arts 2016 - 2018 Rowan University Transfer Credit 2012 - 2015 Atlantic Cape CC H.S. Diploma 2008 - 2012 Winslow Twp HS